slixa.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy | Slixa

Effective Date: _Sept 26, 2012_

Last Updated: _Sept 26, 2012_

#### 1\. Definitions

> 1.1 You, the User — As the user of this site, this policy will occasionally refer to the user as “You” or through any second-person pronouns, such as “Your,” or “Yours,” etc. 
> 
> 1.2 We, the Owner — as the owner of the Website(s), this policy will occasionally refer to Slixa as “Us” or “We”, or through any second-person pronouns, such as “Our,” or “Ours,” etc. 
> 
> 1.3 When the terms “the Website(s)”, “the Website” or simply “Website(s)” are used, these terms refer to www.slixa.com, e.slixa.com, or any other website owned and operated by Slixa.

#### 2\. General Provisions

> 2.1 Slixa is the publisher and operator of the website slixa.com. The Website is an online service that permits individuals to create advertisement profiles for display in Our online directory. Only adult members of the public may browse these advertisements or use the Website(s) in any way. 
> 
> 2.2 Slixa respects Your privacy and complies with all applicable privacy and data protection laws. This Privacy Policy describes how We use information received about You when You visit Our Website(s) or when You subscribe to, or otherwise use Our online services. Please read it carefully and be sure You understand how Your information is collected and used. This Policy does not cover any information that We may receive from or about You through channels other than the use of the Website(s).
> 
> 2.3 Slixa.com may contain links to outside websites. Slixa is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of those outside sites. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on slixa.com or any other Slixa Website(s).

#### 3\. Revisions To This Policy

> 3.1 Slixa reserves the right to revise or amend this and other Policies at any time for any reason. You should periodically review this Policy to see if there have been any modifications. If the “Last Modified” date has changed since You last reviewed this Policy, You may assume that there has been a revision and You are strongly encouraged to re-read it in its entirety. Upon posting, any modified or amended version of this Policy will automatically supersede any prior version. 

#### 4\. Information Slixa Collects from Advertisers and how it is used

> 4.1 By using the Website or providing personal information to Slixa, You are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of Your personal information as described in this Policy. 
> 
> 4.2 Slixa only collects personally identifying information that is knowingly and voluntarily submitted by You, for example, when You fill out a form or create a profile. This information may include Your preferred name, email address, and phone number. Beyond this, Slixa does not engage in active data collection, does not collect personally identifiable information, and does not take steps to verify the accuracy of the information You provide. Unless You are an Advertiser on the website(s), you are not required to provide this information in order to access or use the Website(s); You may use slixa.com or any other Slixa Website anonymously. 
> 
> 4.3 MN collects information that is sent to us automatically by Your web browser as well as data gathered from Google® analytics. This information typically includes the IP address of Your Internet service provider, the name of Your operating system (such as OSX® or Windows®) and the name and version of Your browser (such as Google Chrome® or Firefox®). The information We receive depends on the settings on Your web browser. Please check Your browser if You want to learn what information Your browser sends or how to change Your settings.
> 
> 4.4 Our Website(s) uses two types of cookies on its Website(s). The first, a session cookie, is used to tag Your computer with a computer-generated, unique identifier when You access our site. A session cookie does not identify You personally and expires after You close Your browser. The second type of cookie is a “persistent cookie”. These cookies do not expire after You close Your Browser and will remain on Your computer unless and until You delete them. 
> 
> 4.5 If You are visiting Slixa.com or any other of Slixa’s sites by clicking on one of our affiliate’s links, a cookie containing the affiliate’s identifier will be stored on Your computer for one year.
> 
> 4.6 If You do not wish to use cookies, You may set Your browser to reject cookies or to alert You when a cookie is placed on Your computer. Although You are not required to accept cookies when You visit a Slixa Internet Site, You may be unable to use all of the functionality of the site if Your browser rejects Our cookies. However, cookies must be enabled if You intend to log in to Your account on the Website.

#### 5\. The Use of Information Collected

> 5.1 Slixa primary purpose for information collected from You is to provide You with products and/or services You may have requested or be interested in. For example, if You provide Your e-mail address and/or sign up to receive e-mail alerts, we may use Your e-mail address to deliver the e-mail alerts You request.
> 
> 5.2 Slixa uses cookies to collect information about Users in order to improve and enhance the experience on, and use of, the Website. Collected information may include, but is not limited to, the User’s IP Address, guest ID, geographic location, preferences, and other data unique to a particular session of use on the Website. 
> 
> 5.3 Slixa may also use Your information to deliver customized services, for support purposes, and for the prevention of fraud, spamming, harassment, and other undesirable online activity to the extent permissible by applicable law. 
> 
> 5.4 Slixa may also occasionally use non-personal and aggregate information, such as passively collected information as described above. The purpose for this use is to tailor marketing or to customize use of the Website for an aggregate group of Users for market research purposes e.g., to increase the overall experience for all Users, to analyze and target new markets and market potential, or for other marketing purposes. 
> 
> 5.5 Slixa uses the information provided by Your browser to create statistics that help us improve our sites and make them more compatible with the technology used by our Internet visitors.

#### 6\. How information is shared

> 6.1 It is Slixa’s policy not to use or share information about You in ways not described in this policy without first presenting You with an opportunity to opt out of, or object to, such uses. However, we may disclose a Your information if there is a reasonable basis for doing so, including the following:
>
>> 6.1.1 To comply with any laws including, but not limited to, the Electronic Communications Privacy Act or any other legal or governmental requests for information; 
>> 
>> 6.1.2 If disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or to bring legal action against a person who may be in violation of Slixa Terms and Conditions;
>> 
>> 6.1.3 As is reasonably necessary to operate the Website;
>> 
>> 6.1.4 To protect Slixa, its Users, its Advertisers, and the general public. Slixa will only disclose a User’s information when it is compelled and /or required to do so by law (for example, in response to a court order or subpoena). Where permitted by law, Slixa will not disclose any information pertaining to any User without first presenting the User with an opportunity to object to said disclosure.
>> 
>> 6.1.5 Slixa shares as little information as possible with its affiliates. The only information shared with any affiliate will be limited to the number of new accounts created on slixa.com that resulted from the affiliate relationship and the date and time the account(s) were created. 

#### 7\. How information is kept secure

> 7.1 We use all reasonable measures to protect Your personally identifying information that is stored within our database (including data encryption, SSL, strong password requirements and firewalls), and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. While we take all reasonable measures to secure and protect Your information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse or alteration, as is the case with all computer networks linked to the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control. Please remember that any information you make publicly available will not be encrypted. 

#### 8\. Communications from Slixa

> 8.1 To the extent that You have provided Your email address to Slixa You may, from time to time, receive promotional communications from Us to advertise products and services You may be interested in. 

#### 9\. Special Provision for Minors

> 9.1 Slixa.com and other Slixa sites ARE NOT intended for persons under the age of majority in their jurisdiction. Slixa does not solicit or collect personal information from or about children on its Website(s). It is a violation of Slixa policy and Federal law for any person under the age of majority to use, access, or be featured on slixa.com or any other Slixa website. If You suspect that a minor has used, or is being featured on, any Slixa website, please contact us immediately at [legal@slixa.com](mailto:legal@slixa.com). 

If You have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [legal@slixa.com](mailto:legal@slixa.com)
